<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pointless Expectations</title>
    <link>https://babak4.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Pointless Expectations</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 May 2015 16:12:15 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://babak4.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Author</title>
      <link>https://babak4.github.io/about-author/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 16:02:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://babak4.github.io/about-author/</guid>
      <description>Babak Tourani
Currently:
 Data Engineer at Vonage (previously known as Nexmo) Databases: Oracle, Redshift, Snowflake Workflow Orchestrators: Airflow, Oozie Languages: [PL/]SQL, Python, Java  Formerly:
 TV/Radio presenter and producer (BBC World Service) Basketball Coach. Assistant Coach of Iran&amp;rsquo;s Basketball Team  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disclaimer</title>
      <link>https://babak4.github.io/disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 15:56:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://babak4.github.io/disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>Dear Reader!
I hereby declare that the material published in this blog have no other purpose, but to remind me about those aspects of the technologies that I use on a daily basis - to earn money, primarily - but I tend to forget quickly.
Also I hope that the posts could help finding [possible] solutions easier on the web, by simply spreading the word, and increasing the exposure of posts&amp;rsquo; subjects to search engines such as Google.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nobody Reads Your Blog!</title>
      <link>https://babak4.github.io/posts/nobody-reads-your-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2015 16:12:15 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://babak4.github.io/posts/nobody-reads-your-blog/</guid>
      <description>Yes, nobody!
I mean: REALLY read it; going through all the words and sentences and paragraphs and get through to the end.
During the time that I was working for BBC World Service (2002-2012) one of the more important guidelines for online content producers was: &amp;ldquo;All you have to play with is the first page, and in fact, first paragraph of your piece. You have to grab your audience&amp;rsquo;s attention there, and say whatever you want to say in the top part of the page, before the user needs to scroll down, because they rarely do!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>